# **WASEEM KASHIF**

## **FULL STACK DEVELOPER**

Flat 210, Block 28, Ansar Gallery Barwa., Doha, portfolio, Qatar | waseemqulandar@gmail.com | 30078398 | https://profile-portfolio-nine.vercel.app/



#### **PROFILE**

Passionate Full Stack Web Developer with a knack for creating intuitive and high-performing web applications. I excel at motivating, mentoring & developing teams of less experienced developers. I have 6 years of experience and ambitious web design professional seeking an opportunity as a web developer. Detail-oriented professional with an associate degree in computer science and proven experience with a web development firm and E-commerce Group.

Please visit my website to see projects I have done: https://profile-portfolio-nine.vercel.app/

## **PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE**

#### Senior Web Developer, Ansar Gallery, A&H MARKET, Doha, Qatar

March 2024 — Present

- Lead development of features for ansargallery.com, enhancing user experience and functionality.
- Implement responsive design using HTML, CSS, and JavaScript frameworks, ensuring compatibility across devices.

## Web Developer, Uconnect Technologies, Gilgit, Pakistan

December 2021 — February 2024

- Developed 10+ responsive websites from Figma designs using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and React.js.
- Collaborated with cross-functional teams to deliver high-quality web applications on time.
- Implemented REST APIs to enhance application functionality and user experience.
- Mentored junior developers, fostering skill development and knowledge sharing.
- · Utilized Git for version control, ensuring efficient project management and collaboration.

## Junior Frontend Developer, Uconnect Technologies, Gilgit, Pakistan January 2021 — December 2021

Worked on various web development projects. Responsible for converting figma designs into real time responsive web applications using required technologies.

#### **Technical Support Engineer, StromFiber, Karachi**

August 2020 — December 2020

• For 6 months I worked as an IT Support Engineer for StromFiber Internet Services, a leading company providing GIPON internet to major cities in Pakistan.

#### **EDUCATION**

## **Bachelor's in Computer Science**

May 2016 — July 2020

Iqra University , Karachi, Pakistan

HOSC II

July 2013 — July 2015

Aga Khan Higher Secondary School, Karachi

## **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

HTML	CSS	JavaScript	Rest API's
Next.js	TypeScript	GIT	Prisma
React.js	Vue.js	SvelteKit	Redux
Tailwind CSS	Material UI	Magento	Next-Auth
Node Js	Express Js		

#### ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

- Links: GitHub, Portfolio,LinkedIn
- Languages: Urdu, English, Shina, Burushki